

FOTO

[Tampilkan foto yang formal dan menunjukan sisi profesionalitas kita]

Muhammad Ikhsan Hamid

PROFILE

Bachelor of physics, enthusiastic, highly motivated and like to explore new things. Experienced in various external and internal campus organizations. Always expand experience and knowledge in software and web development, fullstack developer with node js. Current conducting research on oil palm object detection using computer vision.

KEY SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

[Sebutkan skills yang kamu miliki]

Contoh:

Hardskills – (2022): Data Science Training Certification held by Digitalent Kominfo

Softskills – (2021): Training Organizational 3 held by BEM Riau University

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Laboratorium Fotonik FMIPA Riau University	
Research Assistant	Jan 22 - Jan 23
Research Assistant funded by LPDP	
with letter number PRJ-57/LPDP/2020.	
The research title "Smart Machine	
Vision based on multispectral imaging	
for sorting and grading fresh fruit	
bunches of oil palm" at Riau University	

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

HIMAFI FMIPA UNRI	
Staff PPMB (Pengembangan Potensi Minat dan Bakat)	Apr 2019 - Aug 2020
 a forum for developing the interests and talents of students majoring in physics 	



HIMAFI FMIPA UNRI	
Bupati Mahasiswa	Oct 2020 - Apr 2021
 organize and lead the course of the organization and establish relationship organizations 	with all campus

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

University of Riau	Aug 2018 - Jan 2023
Bachelor's degree, <i>Physics</i> , GPA 3.3/4	

LANGUAGES

Indonesian – Native proficiency (oral and written)English – Professional proficiency (oral and written)